The Reese Family Papers
Marist College Archives and Special Collections
- Graphic Materials, 1850 - 1984; 8; Boxes: 70 - 76 Folders: 1 - 54, 1 - 65, 1 - 81, 1- 46, 1 - 35, 1 - 11, 1 - 17
  - The Oliver Family, 1873 - 1930; 8.6; Boxes: 73 - 76 Folders: 1 - 46, 1 - 35, 1 - 11, 1 - 17
    - Photograph of cattle, Verso: Stonehouse Pandora - 73498; Pant era and Lustre full sister have won; Produce of Aaw[?] Far [illegible] 1919 1st Far [illegible] 1920 1st Trenton 1921 2nd beaten by Lustre 2 daughters Morristown 1921 1st Winner of CC cup donated by New Jersey Guernsey [illegible] 1922 at the Linie[?] State champion record 10451.30 walk[?] 51[?].53 fat; Day of Stonehouse Patrial - Luckey Strike (1st prize bull calf [illegible] 1922) Sue Sir William of Brookwead Dau. Marcia of Upton Payne[?], circa 1922 (Folder 12, Box 74)
    - Photograph of cattle, Verso: Brookweads Primirose[?] 59031. winner of AA cup donated by New Jersey Guernsey Breeders Association - 1922, Record 11341.30 milk, 644.21 fat; Sire. Langwater Stars and Stripes [?] 21872; Dau. [illegible] 32506, circa 1922 (Folder 13, Box 74)
    - Photograph of cattle grazing, labeled Stonehouse Farm, Gladstone, N.J., circa 1922 (Folder 14, Box 74)
    - Photograph of cattle, labeled Stonehouse Farm, Gladstone, N.J., circa 1922 (Folder 15, Box 74)
    - Photograph of cattle, labeled Stonehouse Farm N.J., “Pandora” - F.K. Stevens, Verso: Guernsey Breeders 1st Annual Picnic, Stonehouse Farm, Gladstone, N.J.; Stonehouse Pandora #73498, circa 1922 (Folder 16, Box 74)
    - Photograph of cattle, Francis Kerby Stevens at head, circa 1922 (Folder 17, Box 74)
    - Photograph of cattle, labeled Stonehouse Farm, undated (Folder 18, Box 74)
    - Photograph of Stonehouse Farm in Gladstone, N.J. - home of Francis Kerby Stevens, undated (Folder 19, Box 74)
    - Photograph of House [Stonehouse Farm?], undated (Folder 20, Box 74)
    - Photograph of two children [Elizabeth Shaw Stevens and Frances Gallatin Stevens?], undated (Folder 21, Box 74)
    - Cabinet card of unknown girl, undated (Folder 22, Box 74)
    - Cabinet card of unknown child, undated (Folder 23, Box 74)
    - Mounted photograph of group of people picnicking, labeled: Preicie[?] at Upper Frasier Falls, Murray Bay, includes Elizabeth Shaw Oliver, 1894 (Folder 24, Box 74)
    - Book of 28 photographs, likely from trip to Mexico, undated (Folder 25, Box 74)
    - Large portrait of Elizabeth Shaw Oliver, found in Frame 5, undated (Folder 26, Box 74)
    - Frame 5, undated (Folder 27, Box 74)
    - Cabinet Card of Robert Shaw Oliver, found in Frame 6, 1902 (Folder 28, Box 74)
    - Frame 6, undated (Folder 29, Box 74)
    - Photograph of Nathaniel Oliver, husband of Elizabeth Shaw, found in Frame 7, undated (Folder 30, Box 74)
    - Frame 7, undated (Folder 31, Box 74)
    - Photograph of Elizabeth Shaw, wife of Nathaniel Oliver, found in Frame 8, undated (Folder 32, Box 74)
    - Frame 8, undated (Folder 33, Box 74)
    - Portrait of Marion Oliver, daughter of Robert Shaw Oliver and Marion Rathbone, found in Frame 9, undated (Folder 34, Box 74)
    - Frame 9, undated (Folder 35, Box 74)
    - Sketching of Marion Oliver, found in Frame 10, undated (Folder 1, Box 75)
    - Frame 10, undated (Folder 2, Box 75)
    - Hand-drawn portrait of Lucy Rathbone Bowditch, sister of Marion Rathbone Oliver, signed Bradford Johnson, found in Frame 11, undated (Folder 3, Box 75)
    - Frame 11, undated (Folder 4, Box 75)
    - Mounted Photograph of Elizabeth Shaw Oliver and others riding mules during trip to Mexico, undated (Folder 5, Box 75)
    - Mounted portrait of Elizabeth Shaw Oliver in dress, 2 copies, undated (Folder 6, Box 75)
    - Mounted photograph of bridesmaids, Elizabeth Shaw Oliver on bottom right, undated (Folder 7, Box 75)
    - Large mounted photograph of wedding party, Elizabeth Shaw Oliver second on right of bride, undated (Folder 8, Box 75)
    - Wilfred Lash Robbins, undated (Folder 9, Box 75)
    - “To my dear friend, Lt. Colonel F. N. Garrison, M.D.”, 1928 (Folder 10, Box 75)
    - John Rathbone house, Albany, New York, undated (Folder 11, Box 75)
    - 1. Marion Rathbone Oliver with either John Rathbone Oliver or Elizabeth Shaw Oliver [circa 1873-1874]; 2. Unidentified child [John Rathbone Oliver?]; 3. John Rathbone Oliver [circa 1884]; 4. John Rathbone Oliver [circa 1886], circa 1873 - 1886 (Folder 1, Box 76)
    - John Rathbone Oliver, on a bicycle, portrait photograph [2 items], circa 1882 (Folder 2, Box 76)
    - Sisters Elizabeth Shaw Oliver and Cora Oliver sitting at a table reading [2 items], circa 1880s (Folder 3, Box 76)
    - John Rathbone Oliver, circa 1884 (Folder 4, Box 76)
    - Marion Rathbone Oliver holding Elizabeth Shaw Oliver; John Rathbone Oliver standing, circa 1874 (Folder 5, Box 76)
    - Group of women in winter snowshoes, most likely the Snowshoe Club in Albany, New York, undated (Folder 6, Box 76)
    - St. Paul’s School, New Hampshire; group photo with John Rathbone Oliver, circa 1890 - 1894 (Folder 7, Box 76)
    - “Manor House Grounds”, undated (Folder 8, Box 76)
    - Family at the dining table; Verso: Girl at left looks like Elizabeth Oliver and her dog, “Fetch”, undated (Folder 9, Box 76)
    - John Rathbone Oliver [framed photograph], found in Frame 12, circa 1920 (Folder 10, Box 76)
    - Frame 12, undated (Folder 11, Box 76)
    - Group photograph of John Rathbone Oliver with clergymen, circa 1930s (Folder 12, Box 76)
    - Unidentified photographs taken while John Rathbone Oliver lived and worked in Austria, circa 1910 (Folder 13, Box 76)
    - Unidentified photographs taken while John Rathbone Oliver lived and worked in Austria, circa 1910 (Folder 14, Box 76)
    - Unidentified photographs, undated (Folder 15, Box 76)
    - Unidentified photographs, undated (Folder 16, Box 76)
    - Unidentified photographs, undated (Folder 17, Box 76)
- Administrative Files, 9; Box: 76 Folders: 18 - 25
  Series contains original manuscript finding aid and other related information
  - Original Manuscript Finding Aid prepared by Frances Gallatin Stevens Reese, 9.1; Boxes: 76 Folders: 18 - 24
    - Family Trees, circa 2000 (Folder 18, Box 76)
    - Manuscript Series 1: John Rathbone Oliver Papers, circa 1990s (Folder 19, Box 76)
    - Manuscript Series 3: Elizabeth Shaw Oliver Papers, circa 1990s (Folder 20, Box 76)
    - K: Elizabeth Willard Shaw Oliver Papers (removed from Elizabeth Shaw Oliver Papers), circa 1990s (Folder 21, Box 76)
    - Manuscript Series 4: Francis Kerby Stevens Papers, circa 1990s (Folder 22, Box 76)
    - Manuscript Series 7: Stevens Family Papers, circa 1990s (Folder 23, Box 76)
    - Manuscript Series 9: Ebenezer Stevens Papers, circa 1990s (Folder 24, Box 76)
  - Other related information, 1988; 9.2; Box: 76 Folder: 25
    - The Rathbun-Rathbone-Rathburn Family Historian, volume 8, number 4, October 1988 (Folder 25, Box 76)